let questions=[// Ai
{ numb : 1,
question:"The “Father of Artificial Intelligence” is:",
answer:"John McCarthy",
options:[
"John McCarthy",
"Alan turing  ",
"Charles babbage",
"none"
]
},
{ numb : 2,
question:"Blind Search can be used for which of the following situations?",
answer:"Small search Space",
options:[
"Small search Space",
"Real-life Simulation",
"Advanced Game Theory",
"none"
]
},
{ numb : 3,
question:"In how many category processes is Artificial Intelligence classified in?",
answer:"3",
options:[
"5",
"2",
"3",
"1"
]
},
{ numb : 4,
question:"If a machine can change its course of action based on the external environment on its own, the machine is called?",
answer:"Intelligent",
options:[
"Mobile",
"Intelligent",
"Both A and B",
"None"
]
},
{ numb : 5,
question:"Which of the following is the common language for Artificial Intelligence?",
answer:"Python",
options:[
"Python",
"Php",
"Java",
"lisp"
]
},
{ numb : 6,
question:"Which of the following is not an application of artificial intelligence?",
answer:"Database Management System",
options:[
"Compter vision",
"pattern analysis",
"Database Management System",
"Ai"
]
},
{ numb : 7,
question:"The proposition symbols in AI are?",
answer:"True and False",
options:[
"True and False",
"true",
"False",
"none"
]
},
{ numb : 8,
question:"Which of the following symbols in AI are logical symbols?",
answer:"All of the above",
options:[
"Negation",
"Conjunctiob",
"implication",
"All of the above"
]
},
{ numb : 9,
question:"How many types of recognition are there in AI?",
answer:"3",
options:[
"5",
"3",
"2",
"1"
]
},
{ numb : 10,
question:"Which of the following architecture is also known as systolic arrays?",
answer:"MISD",
options:[
"MISD",
"SISD",
"SIMD",
"None"
]
},
];